tomcruise.com 2018-06-21

# Official Tom Cruise: Reel, Bio, & Filmography

Odin Domains, LLC and its website at www.tomcruise.com (“we,” “our” or “us”) believe that your privacy is very important. This Policy outlines the types of personally identifiable information and other data that we will collect from you through your use of our website (our "Website"), and how we will use and when we might disclose such information and data to third parties. Your installation and/or use of these Website and/or submission of information to us constitute your consent to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 10, 2015 and was last modified on November 18, 2016.

### Definition of the Types of Information Discussed in this Policy:

  1.  **“Personal Information”** is the type of information that specifically identifies you personally and/or can be used alone to contact you online or offline, such as your full name, physical address, email address, telephone number, photograph, precise geolocation information, credit card information and, in some cases, user names; and
  2.  **“Non-personal Information”** is anonymous information about your computer and mobile device, such as your unique device ID, Internet Protocol (IP) address, or other persistent identifiers, and their hardware/software/firmware, as well as data regarding your use of the Website, such as the actions you take within the Website, the browser and/or device you use, and the date and time of your use of the Website.

### Personal Information, Non-personal Information and Other Information That We Collect and How We Collect It

In general, we do not require nor request any Personal Information from you when you use our Website. From time to time, we may offer certain services, such as a newsletter, that will require you to provide us with Personal Information should you choose to take part. In addition, if you reach out to us in any way, or in any other way take steps that require the submission of Personal Information, we would collect whatever Personal Information or any other information you choose to submit and use it for the purposes for which you submitted it.

As noted, we will only collect Personal Information if you choose to submit it to us. However, we, or third party analytics services on our behalf, may collect aggregated, anonymous Usage Data when you use our Website.

A special note about cookies and other identifiers: In connection with the foregoing collection of Usage Data, we may also use cookies or similar technologies (tiny files that are stored on your computer's hard drive or mobile device when you visit certain web pages that identify your computer and may store Usage Data about you). Should you choose to submit Personal Information to us, we may link cookie information to such Personal Information. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, some aspects of our Website will not function properly if you do so and you may lose access to the services you wish to use.

### Use of the Personal Information That We Collect

In the event we collect Personal Information from you, we will only use it to the limited extent required to provide you with the services or functionality you have requested (e.g., to send you a newsletter or e-mail updates) or to respond to your inquiries.

### Use of the Non-personal Information That We Collect

Usage Data in aggregated, anonymous form may be used by us for administrative, analytical, research, optimization, and security purposes.

### Disclosure of the Personal Information and Non-personal Information That We Collect

In the event we offer features that require us to contact you (e.g., newsletter), we may use the services of third party service providers to assist us with executing such features and may be required to share your Personal Information with such service providers for that purpose. In no event will we ever sell, rent or transfer your Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes or for any other reasons other than those described above. Usage Data in aggregated, anonymous form may be shared with third parties who assist us with our internal operations such as administration, analytics, research, and optimization. If we share your Personal Information or Usage Data with third parties as described above, they will be authorized to use such information only for the purposes for which they were engaged.

Our Website may offer social sharing features such as “Share” or “Like” on Facebook or other third party social networking sites. If you decide to use such features, it may allow the sharing and collection of Personal Information and Usage Data both to and from such third-party social networks. In addition, should you choose to submit any Personal Information to or through such social networks, the collection, use and sharing of your Personal Information will be governed by the privacy policies of those social networks, not by this policy. Therefore, you should visit the policies of such third parties for more information about their information collection practices.

Finally, we may share your Personal Information: (i) In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law - in such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us; (ii) When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Use and other agreements; or (iii) In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

### Your Rights

You represent and warrant that all Personal Information you choose to provide us, if any, is true and correct and relates to you and not to any other person.

If you wish to opt out of further communications from us, or if you wish to review, delete and/or revise the Personal Information we have stored about you, please contact us with your specific request at [TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com](mailto:TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com), using “Privacy Request” in the subject line. Please note, however, that we reserve the right to retain an archive of such Personal Information for a commercially reasonable time to ensure that its deletion does not affect the integrity of our data; and we further reserve the right to retain an anonymous version of such information.

You can decline to permit cookies in your browser, but in that case we cannot promise you that all features will function properly as a result.

### Partnerships and External Sources

Our Website may link to external sites beyond our control (e.g., to the websites of studios or specific motion pictures or to related social media accounts). This privacy policy covers only the way we treat the Personal Information and Usage Data we collect on our Website. By accessing any external sites, you are agreeing to the privacy policies of those sites. Please understand that the external sites may have different policies with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information. We have no control over and are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties. Therefore, you are encouraged to review the privacy policies of all third-party websites. Without limiting anything in the following section, we are not liable in any way for the actions, inactions or policies of any external services.

### Children

Our Website is intended for use by adults only and we do not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent of a child under 13 years of age and you believe your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at [TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com](mailto:TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com), using “Delete Information” in the subject line, and we will delete the information from our system.

### Your California Privacy Rights

Under certain circumstances, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 requires that, upon receipt of a request by a customer residing in California, a business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year for direct marketing purposes, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed. However, the foregoing does not apply to businesses like ours that do not disclose Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes without prior approval or that give customers a free mechanism to opt out of having their personal information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Users residing in California may request further information about our approach to this law by writing to us at [TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com](mailto:TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com), using the subject line “CA Request for Information,” and requesting further information.

Do Not Track Disclosures in California: due to technological limitations, we cannot guarantee that our Website will be able to abide by any “do not track” technology that you may choose to utilize.

### Changes

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. In the event we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, such policy will be re-posted in the "Privacy" section of our Website with the date such modifications were made indicated on the top of the page. Therefore, please review this Privacy Policy from time to time so that you are aware when any changes are made to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after such change constitutes your acceptance of any such change(s), and if you do not accept any changes, you may choose not to use the Website or opt out by sending us an appropriate notice. If you would like more information about any material changes we have made to the Privacy Policy in a recent update, please contact us with your request at [TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com](mailto:TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com), using “Information About Update” in the subject line.

### Security

It is entirely your choice whether or not you provide Personal Information to us. We and/or our third-party partners have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to attempt to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the Personal Information collected through the Website. We take, or obligate applicable third parties to take, reasonable precautions to protect our customers' Personal Information against loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, please remember that no transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us or from us, and you do so at your own risk. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by email and you do so at your own risk.

If you believe your Personal Information is being improperly used by us or any third party, please immediately contact us at [TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com](mailto:TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com) using “Security Concern” in the subject line.

### Legal Disclaimer

All other terms governing our agreement with respect to your use of the Website can be found in our Terms of Use.

If you have any general questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com](mailto:TomCruiseTeam@gmail.com).
